Nighttime and Idol
Music.
Yes, sir.
This is music.
What kind of music?
Yes, of course.
Of course, at Ebituaries, we have been exposed to a great variety
I've been exposed to various genres of music.
I feel the joy of music there, too.
I've been able to listen to various genres of music
I started to listen to various genres of music
I became very interested in sound creation
I became very interested in making sounds
After I became an adult
When I was about 20 years old
I started writing songs.
I've released an original song at my solo birthday concert.
I was allowed to perform at a music event in January for the first time as a solo artist, and I played as a DJ there.
I've been steadily working on various musical activities.
For me, music is a moment when I can really open myself up and have fun.
It's a moment when I can really laugh from the bottom of my heart and have fun, and it's something that I really enjoy doing.
It's something I really enjoy doing, so I think it's an important element.
I think it's an important element.
Hmmm...
It's Ebikyu-san, isn't it?
I've heard that a lot of artists
I've seen a lot of artists put up guttick theses.
I was shocked by that...
I was shocked to know that this kind of music exists.
Did you have any encounters with Mr. Tetsu Okazaki, who was the one who inspired me to use dtm to write songs?
I met Tetsu Okazaki, who started out writing songs at his study desk in his parents' house in Kyoto, and then went on to write the theme song for Pokemon and become an artist loved even by children.
I admired him a lot and was impressed by how much he enjoyed what he did.
I got the impression that he was having a lot of fun doing it, and that's when I bought a computer and started writing songs.
That was a great encounter for me.
Is there any particular part that is difficult for you or that you are working hard on right now? Well, if I had to say the difficult part, I guess I would have to say what it is.
I don't want to sound like I'm trying to be cool, but making music is not something that you can do just because you want to do it.
It's something you can do when you feel it.
So even if you sit down at your desk and try to make music
I have a lot of trouble moving forward.
But when I was out with Fuller
I'm out with Fuller, and I suddenly feel like, "How about this kind of melody?
I always have a hard time finding the right timing when my head is spinning and I'm motivated to create.
Jas in space
I remember the moment when it was outside, the moment it started falling.
You remember that song "Blue Sky Gift" which was the first song I wrote when I decided to write a song for the first time.
That song was written when I was walking down the street and I suddenly remembered this thing that I cherish.
I suddenly remembered that I wanted to write lyrics like this or sing a melody like this.
Then I went home and recorded it.
I went home and recorded it.
I'll listen to it, too.
See, it's good, isn't it?
The kettle and the idol
I want to make this room smart.
I'd like to be in the room with the smartest person in the room.
Mr. Cassy.
Mr. Hy007
Bright Red Tomato
Ayana!
Mr. and Mrs. Paripi and their brothers provided this program.
Thank you very much!